<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foss on Dragons Lair</title>
    <link>https://dr460nf1r3.org/tags/foss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foss on Dragons Lair</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>:copyright: 2021-2024 [dr460nf1r3](https://dr460nf1r3.org)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:00:40 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dr460nf1r3.org/tags/foss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Improving Garuda&#39;s repository set via CI/CD pipelines</title>
      <link>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/garuda-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/garuda-ci/</guid>
      <description>This is another post dedicated to recent changes to some of our infrastructure - this time tackling the repository setups, particularly those containing PKGBUILDs or sources for our packages &amp;#x1f527;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking the infra&#39;s NixOS setup to the next level</title>
      <link>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/nix-infra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/nix-infra/</guid>
      <description>This is a summary about the most recent major server maintenance we had at Garuda Linux / Chaotic-AUR &amp;#x1f527;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ansible roles for the infra!</title>
      <link>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/ansible-infra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/ansible-infra/</guid>
      <description>As our infrastructure is growing, the number of services and tasks is increasing as well. This can be tedious and time-consuming, especially when you have to deal with a lot of servers - enter Ansible! Ansible allows automating tasks on a wide range of platforms, including Linux, Windows, and Mac. &amp;#x1f527;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garuda Linux</title>
      <link>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/garuda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/garuda/</guid>
      <description>For about 2 years I have been using Linux. Since the beginning, I loved the way things work on Linux, the simplicity and customizability - something unheard of in among windows users. A long time of these two years I spent distro hopping, searching for the optimal Linux distribution for my requirements. &amp;#x1f985;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FireDragon browser</title>
      <link>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/firedragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dr460nf1r3.org/projects/firedragon/</guid>
      <description>Recently we got to know that Mozilla no longer supports free internet. Their browser, Firefox, collects a lot of telemetry by default. Since using Chromium-based browsers is not an alternative (There shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a single browser engine dictating web standards! &amp;#x1f440;), a better solution had to be found!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
